var quizList = [
	{
		question: "True or False: Javascript arrays can hold any type of value, even different types within the same array.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: "True or False: Javascript is a strongly typed language, meaning all variables must be declared as their data type: int, string, and so on.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: "True or False: innerText, innerHTML, and textContent all reference the same part of an HTML element.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: "True or Fale: The structure of Javascript objects is immutable; extra fields cannot be added.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: "True or False: The '===' is for comparing values strictly, while the '==' allows looser comparison instead.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: "True or False: Not only are [square brackets] used to declare arrays, they are also used to access the items inside.",
		choices: [ "True", "False" ],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these methods is NOT valid for incrementing a variable called 'index'?",
		choices: [ "index++;", "index += 1;", "increment index;", "index = index + 1;" ],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the object used for storing persistent data for a web page?",
		choices: [ "settingStorage", "cookieManager", "dataBucket", "localStorage" ],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: "Variables that are declared outside of any functions or objects are known as what kind of variables?",
		choices: [ "Global", "Super", "Local", "Universal" ],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these methods is the correct way to start a for loop?",
		choices: [ "for (var i = 0; i < 10)", "for (var i = 0; i < 10; i++)", "for (var i = 1 to 10)", "for (var i = 0; i < 10; i + 1)" ],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: "We often use the acronym 'DRY' as a best practice.  What does this mean?",
		choices: [ "Don't Rush Yourself", "Divide, Refactor, Yield", "Don't Repeat Yourself", "Dummies Really Yeet" ],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: "What is code {enclosed in curly braces} known as?",
		choices: [ "A block", "A bucket", "Grouped", "Sequestered"],
		correct: 0
	}
];